And so the Nobel Peace Prize will be announced on Friday.
You've been nominated by many world leaders.
By many, many countries.
That's right.
By many countries, as well as the hostage families.
Do you think you will win?
I have no idea.
I mean, look, I did settle.
Marco would tell you we settled seven wars.
We're close to settling an eighth.
And I think we'll end up settling the Russia
situation, which is horrible.
7,000 people died last week, by the way,
in Russia, between Russia and Ukraine.
I think we'll settle that.
So I don't think anybody in history has settled that many.
But perhaps they'll find a reason not to give it to me.
You know?
Perhaps they will.
Mr. President, thank you so much, Mr. President.
Thank you.
Going to the shutdown quickly, what
is your position on the extension of health care
subsidies, which is what Democrats are asking for?
All I want to do is very simple.
I want to get the country open.
And then we're going to discuss that.
And we'd like to.
Obamacare is a horrible mess.
And it has been from the beginning.
We want to make it better, stronger.
Even if it costs more money, it costs more money.
We want to make it better.
The Democrats want to make it worse.
The Democrats want to approve health care for illegals
coming into our country, many of them
coming in from prisons, and mental institutions,
and drug dealers.
They want to give them health care.
We don't want that for our people,
because that's going to destroy the health care
that we already have.
We'd like to make Obamacare better, better for people,
less expensive, and better health care.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. President, I'm wondering if you've
been briefed on the organization and funding of Antifa.
And if so, what have you learned?
I have been.
And they have pretty good knowledge.
But they're going to have a very good knowledge.
And I really ask these very brave patriots
that we're surrounded with today to let us know,
because I think you probably have some pretty good ideas.
And even if you're not sure, let us know,
and we'll figure it out, OK?
If you could do that.
I don't know.
I'm not from the Middle East.
Can you specify?
You're from Italy?
No.
I'm from France.
Can you specify how close we are to the deal?
Would that be announced today or tomorrow?
And do you want to see the hostages released before you
travel to the region?
No.
I think I'll probably go maybe before the hostages are
released, or shortly thereafter, pretty much shortly thereafter.
Yeah, please.
I'm not participating in any of the negotiations.
Mr. President.
Go ahead.
Who are you with?
The center square.
I had the honor of asking you originally
if you would designate Antifa a terror organization.
And I stand here before you today,
and I'm echoing what Andy said over here.
Are you going to work with your administration
as the Secretary of State's here?
to designate it a foreign terror organization?
You mean it a terror?
Antifa.
A foreign terror organization.
Well, has that been done?
Pretty close, right?
Would you like to see it done?
Yes, Mr. President.
Do you think it would help?
They have foreign links all across Western Europe.
I'd be glad to do it.
I think it's the kind of thing I'd like to do.
If you'd like to.
Does everybody agree?
If you agree, I agree.
Let's get it done, OK?
Let's get it done.
Marco, we'll take care of it.
Mr. President.
That's international, you mean.
International.
Sounds good to me.
Steve, are you OK with it?